Guide to the Greenwich House Records TAM.139
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series VIII: Greenwich House post-Simkhovitch records (NOT microfilmed)
  - Subseries 3: Maxwell Powers Files
    - Lower West Side Anti-Poverty Board- proposals for programs, ca.1965 (Box 94, Folder 37)
    - Lower West Side Anti-Poverty Program- statement in defense of program (by Powers), 1965 (Box 94, Folder 38)
    - Narcotics- Case Work; Cases A-Z, 1955-1962 (Box 94, Folder 39)
    - Narcotics- correspondence, 1956-1963 (Box 94, Folder 40)
    - Neighborhood Youth Corps, 1965-1968 (Box 94, Folder 41)
    - Old Age Program, 1965-1966 (Box 94, Folder 42)
    - Powers, Maxwell- personal, 1965-1966 (Box 94, Folder 43)
    - Powers, Maxwell- trip to Europe, 1965 (Box 94, Folder 44)
    - Public Relations, 1960-1966 (Box 94, Folder 45)
    - Reference letters for GH employees, 1957-1965 (Box 94, Folder 46)
    - Remedial Reading Program, 1965-1966 (Box 94, Folder 47)
    - Summer Adult Office Training Program, 1965 (Box 94, Folder 48)
    - Summer Teen Office Training Program, 1965 (Box 94, Folder 49)
    - Summer Teen Office Training Program, 1966 (Box 94, Folder 50)
    - Transit Strike- correspondence with Senators, 1966 (Box 94, Folder 51)
    - Waterfront Commission of NY Harbor; Balducci, Michael, 1960 (Box 94, Folder 52)
    - Waterfront Commission of NY Harbor; Ciaffone, Vito - Cooke, John, 1958-1965 (Box 94, Folder 53)
    - Waterfront Commission of NY Harbor; Donovan, Francis, 1957-1958 (Box 94, Folder 54)
    - Waterfront Commission of NY Harbor; Garvey, James, 1957-1958 (Box 94, Folder 55)
    - Waterfront Commission of NY Harbor; Harris, Richard; LaRocca, Joseph, 1959-1964 (Box 94, Folder 56)
    - Waterfront Commission of NY Harbor; Manoogian, Michael, 1960-1962 (Box 94, Folder 57)
    - Waterfront Commission of NY Harbor; Margiotta, Ferdinand; Mauro, Edward, 1957-1964 (Box 94, Folder 58)
    - Waterfront Commission of NY Harbor; Messina, Angelo - Platner, Raymond, 1954-1964 (Box 94, Folder 59)
    - Waterfront Commission of NY Harbor; Rizzotti, Christopher; Santiago, Henry, 1959-1964 (Box 94, Folder 60)
    - Waterfront Commission of NY Harbor; Sherman, Joseph, 1957-1961 (Box 94, Folder 61)
    - Waterfront Commission of NY Harbor; Tockarshewsky, Joseph; Troy, Gerard, 1958-1962 (Box 94, Folder 62)
    - Waterfront Commission of NY Harbor; Uliano, Leo J., 1958-1959 (Box 94, Folder 63)
    - West Side Association of Community Centers, 1964-1966 (Box 94, Folder 64)
    - West Side Association of Community Centers- minutes, 1965-1966 (Box 94, Folder 65)
  - Subseries 4: Fundraising
    - Contribution Correspondence- Individuals (alphabetically)
      - Contribution Correspondence A-G, 1969-1970 (Box 95, Folder 1)
      - Contribution Correspondence H-M, 1969-1970 (Box 95, Folder 2)
      - Contribution Correspondence N-Z, 1969-1970 (Box 95, Folder 3)
      - Powers- Contribution Correspondence A-B, 1973 (Box 95, Folder 4)
      - Powers- Contribution Correspondence C-F, 1973 (Box 95, Folder 5)
      - Powers- Contribution Correspondence G-J, 1973 (Box 95, Folder 6)
      - Powers- Contribution Correspondence K-L, 1973 (Box 95, Folder 7)
      - Powers- Contribution Correspondence M-Q, 1973 (Box 95, Folder 8)
      - Powers- Contribution Correspondence R-S, 1973 (Box 95, Folder 9)
      - Powers- Contribution Correspondence T-W, 1973 (Box 95, Folder 10)
      - Appeal letters, 1973-1974 (Box 95, Folder 11)
      - Powers- Contribution Correspondence A, 1974-1975 (Box 95, Folder 12)
      - Powers- Contribution Correspondence B, 1974-1976 (Box 95, Folder 13)
      - Powers- Contribution Correspondence C-D, 1974-1976 (Box 95, Folder 14)
      - Powers- Contribution Correspondence E-G, 1974-1976 (Box 95, Folder 15)
      - Powers- Contribution Correspondence H, 1974-1976 (Box 95, Folder 16)
      - Powers- Contribution Correspondence I-K, 1974-1976 (Box 95, Folder 17)
      - Powers- Contribution Correspondence N-Q, 1974-1976 (Box 95, Folder 18)
      - Powers- Contribution Correspondence L-M, -1974-1976 (Box 95, Folder 19)
      - Powers- Contribution Correspondence R-S, -1976 (Box 95, Folder 20)
      - Powers- Contribution Correspondence T-Z, 1974-1976 (Box 95, Folder 21)
    - Foundations
      - Avalon Foundation, 1954-1967 (Box 95, Folder 22)
      - Beinecke Foundation, 1962-1968 (Box 95, Folder 23)
      - Leonard Bernstein Foundation, 1966-1974 (Box 95, Folder 24)
      - Simon & Annie Davis Foundation, 1976-1979 (Box 95, Folder 25)
      - Edgar Fairchild/Fairchild Publications, 1974-1979 (Box 95, Folder 26)
      - Fanton Foundation, 1972-1975 (Box 95, Folder 27)
      - Grand Street Boys' Foundation, 1963-1974 (Box 95, Folder 28)
      - Greater NY Coalition on Drug Abuse, 1977 (Box 95, Folder 29)
      - Greenwich Village Fresh Air Fund, 1965-1975 (Box 95, Folder 30)
      - Mary Harriman Trust, 1969-1982 (Box 95, Folder 31)
      - Hochschild Fund, Inc., 1962-1975 (Box 95, Folder 32)
      - Huber Foundation, 1970-1981 (Box 95, Folder 33)
      - Kempner Foundation, Inc., 1969-1973 (Box 95, Folder 34)
      - Kiwanis Club of Greenwich Village, 1964-1979 (Box 95, Folder 35)
      - Edith & Herbert Lehman Foundation, Inc., 1966-1987 (Box 95, Folder 36)
      - John Lindsley Fund, 1966-1970 (Box 95, Folder 37)
      - Mallory Family Foundation, 1962-1971 (Box 95, Folder 38)
      - McGraw-Hill Foundation, 1979-1981 (Box 95, Folder 39)
      - Charles Merrill Trust, 1957-1981 (Box 95, Folder 40)
      - Ingram Merrill Foundation, 1967-1973 (Box 95, Folder 41)
      - Ernestine Meyer, 1967-1977 (Box 95, Folder 42)
      - Cecil & George Naumburg Foundation, 1962-1983 (Box 95, Folder 43)
      - Ottens Family Foundation, 1967-1975 (Box 95, Folder 44)
      - Ox Hollow Foundation, 1971-1981 (Box 95, Folder 45)
      - Henry Pearlman Foundation, 1965-1974 (Box 95, Folder 46)
      - Pope Foundation, 1976-1981 (Box 95, Folder 47)
      - J. A. Preston Corporation, 1973-1975 (Box 95, Folder 48)
      - Prudential Savings Bank (formerly West Side Savings Bank), 1963-1976 (Box 95, Folder 49)
      - Herman E. Simon Charitable Trust, 1967-1990 (Box 95, Folder 50)
      - Stephanie Takacs Scholarship Fund, 1972-1975 (Box 95, Folder 51)
      - Tiro A. Segno of NY, Inc., 1969-1979 (Box 95, Folder 52)
      - Leo & Margaret Shaw Foundation, Inc., 1968-1979 (Box 95, Folder 53)
      - The Socolow Foundation, 1969-1975 (Box 95, Folder 54)
      - Turrell Fund, 1958-1964 (Box 95, Folder 55)
      - West Side Association of Community Centers, Inc., 1971-1981 (Box 95, Folder 56)
      - West Side Association of Youth Foundation, Inc., 1963-1981 (Box 95, Folder 57)
      - Wollman Foundation, 1958-1961 (Box 95, Folder 58)
      - Contribution Correspondence- Foundations; A-Z, 1971-1983 (Box 95, Folder 59)
    - Contributions
      - Contribution Correspondence- A, 1965-1968 (Box 96, Folder 1)
      - Contribution Correspondence- B, 1964-1969 (Box 96, Folder 2)
      - Contribution Correspondence- C, 1965-1969 (Box 96, Folder 3)
      - Contribution Correspondence- D, 1965-1969 (Box 96, Folder 4)
      - Contribution Correspondence- E-F, 1965-1969 (Box 96, Folder 5)
      - Contribution Correspondence- G, 1965-1969 (Box 96, Folder 6)
      - Contribution Correspondence- H, 1965-1969 (Box 96, Folder 7)
      - Contribution Correspondence- I-J, 1965-1969 (Box 96, Folder 8)
      - Contribution Correspondence- K, 1964-1968 (Box 96, Folder 9)
      - Contribution Correspondence- L, 1965-1969 (Box 96, Folder 10)
      - Contribution Correspondence- M, 1965-1969 (Box 96, Folder 11)
      - Contribution Correspondence- M, 1965-1969 (Box 96, Folder 12)
      - Contribution Correspondence- N-Q, 1965-1969 (Box 96, Folder 13)
      - Contribution Correspondence- R, 1965-1969 (Box 96, Folder 14)
      - Contribution Correspondence- S, 1965-1969 (Box 96, Folder 15)
      - Contribution Correspondence- S, 1965-1969 (Box 96, Folder 16)
      - Contribution Correspondence- T, 1965-1969 (Box 96, Folder 17)
      - Contribution Correspondence- U-V, 1965-1969 (Box 96, Folder 18)
      - Contribution Correspondence- W, 1965-1969 (Box 96, Folder 19)
      - Contribution Correspondence- W-Z, 1965-1969 (Box 96, Folder 20)
      - Contribution Correspondence- Foundations; A-L, 1954-1968 (Box 96, Folder 21)
      - Contribution Correspondence- Foundations; M-Z, 1963-1969 (Box 96, Folder 22)
      - Fundraising- printed materials, undated (Box 97, Folder 1)
      - Camp Appeals- letters, undated (Box 97, Folder 2)
      - Contributions- monthly reports, 1969-1971 (Box 97, Folder 3)
      - Contributions- special appeals- monthly reports, 1967-1969 (Box 97, Folder 4)
      - Contributions- special appeals- camp, undated (Box 97, Folder 5)
      - Newsletter Greenwich House Gazette, undated (Box 97, Folder 6)
      - Christmas Appeals- letters, 1972-1973, undated (Box 97, Folder 7)
      - Special Events- Annual Luncheon, 1974 (Box 97, Folder 8)
      - Thrift Shop, undated (Box 97, Folder 9)
      - Christmas Celebrations, 1975 (Box 97, Folder 10)
      - Christmas Appeals- printed materials, 1970s (Box 97, Folder 11)
      - Camp Appeals- printed materials, 1970s (Box 97, Folder 12)
      - Contributions- special appeals- Christmas, undated (Box 97, Folder 13)
      - Contributions- special appeals, 1976 (Box 97, Folder 14)
      - Contributions- monthly reports, 1974-1976 (Box 97, Folder 15)
      - Contributions- monthly reports, 1966-1967 (Box 97, Folder 16)
      - Contributions- special appeals- monthly reports, 1974-1975 (Box 97, Folder 17)
      - Contributions- special appeals- monthly reports, 1966 (Box 97, Folder 18)
      - Contributions- monthly reports, 1972-1973 (Box 97, Folder 19)
  - Subseries 5: New York House & School of Industry (NYHSI)
    - Financial Records- correspondence, undated (Box 98, Folder 1)
    - By Laws, 1927, 1941-1942 (Box 98, Folder 2)
    - Notes on history of NYHSI, undated (Box 98, Folder 3)
    - Consolidation with Cooperative Social Settlement Society, 1950-1951 (Box 98, Folder 4)
    - Annual report- excerpt, 1864 (Box 98, Folder 5)
    - Annual reports, 1899-1902 (Box 98, Folder 6)
    - Annual reports, 1910-1913 (Box 98, Folder 7)
    - Annual reports, 1914-1917 (Box 98, Folder 8)
    - Annual reports, 1918-1922 (Box 98, Folder 9)
    - Annual reports, 1923-1927 (Box 98, Folder 10)
    - Annual reports, 1928-1930, 1932-1933 (Box 98, Folder 11)
    - Annual reports, 1934-1937 (Box 98, Folder 12)
    - Annual report materials, 1951, 1955 (Box 98, Folder 13)
    - Annual reports- correspondence re holdings in other repositories, 1898-1935 (Box 98, Folder 14)
    - Advisory Committee, 1950-1951 (Box 98, Folder 15)
    - Evaluation Committee- Report on Relations with Greenwich House; McDowell Report, 1954 (Box 98, Folder 16)
    - Evaluation Committee Report & McDowell Report- correspondence, 1954 (Box 98, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence re Committee minutes, 1954 (Box 98, Folder 18)
    - Committee- member list, ca.1950 (Box 98, Folder 19)
    - Minutes, undated (Box 98, Folder 20)
    - Minutes, 1951-1952 (Box 98, Folder 21)
    - Minutes, 1953-1954 (Box 98, Folder 22)
    - Director's correspondence, 1952-1957 (Box 98, Folder 23)
    - Director's correspondence w/ Archdiocesan Vocational Service, 1952-1957 (Box 98, Folder 24)
    - Director's correspondence w/ Federation Employment Service, 1952-1957 (Box 98, Folder 25)
    - Director's correspondence w/ NY State Employment Service, 1952-1957 (Box 98, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence of Director of Greenwich House, 1950-1954 (Box 98, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence of Director of Greenwich House, 1955 (Box 98, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence with President/ Chairman, 1950-1953 (Box 98, Folder 29)
    - Secretary's correspondence- Charity Organization Society, 1910-1913 (Box 98, Folder 30)
    - Treasurer's correspondence with Accountant Mary Cornell, 1936-1945 (Box 98, Folder 31)
    - Treasurer's correspondence w/ Attorney Louis Mead Treadwell, 1941-1942 (Box 98, Folder 32)
    - Treasurer's correspondence with Central Hanover Bank, 1942-1945 (Box 98, Folder 33)
    - Treasurer's correspondence w/ Central Hanover Bank- agreements, 1942-1945 (Box 98, Folder 34)
    - Treasurer's correspondence- insurance, 1939-1951 (Box 98, Folder 35)
    - Treasurer's correspondence- mortgages (Cravath, deGersdoff, Swain and Wood), 1943 (Box 98, Folder 36)
    - Treasurer's correspondence- mortgages (Ivor Clarke, Inc), 1936-1941 (Box 98, Folder 37)
    - Treasurer's correspondence- mortgages (Rutland & Benjamin, Inc., 1941-1944 (Box 98, Folder 38)
    - Treasurer's correspondence- Stocks & Bonds (RL Day & Co), 1928-1942 (Box 98, Folder 39)
    - Treasurer's correspondence- tax exemption, 1928-1940 (Box 98, Folder 40)
    - Treasurer's correspondence- miscellaneous, 1938-1946 (Box 98, Folder 41)
    - Minutes- Alumnae Group Business Meeting, 1955 (Box 98, Folder 42)
    - Lists of Registered Applicants, 1954-1955 (Box 98, Folder 43)
    - Statistical Surveys on Applicants, 1952-1957 (Box 98, Folder 44)
    - Home Workers- correspondence, permits, lists of workers, 1929-1954 (Box 98, Folder 45)
    - League of Mothers' Clubs, 1931 (Box 98, Folder 46)
    - Printed materials- catalogues of goods sewn, general leaflet, ca.1930, 1951-1952, undated (Box 98, Folder 47)
    - Thursday Sewing Class- annual meetings; member lists, 1931-1939 (Box 98, Folder 48)
    - Thursday Sewing Class- correspondence, 1932-1939 (Box 98, Folder 49)
    - Financial Records- Annual Trial Balances, 1932-1943 (Box 98, Folder 50)
    - Financial Records- Budgets, 1939-1943, ca.1951-1960 (Box 98, Folder 51)
    - Financial Records- Budget Control Reports, 1954 (Box 98, Folder 52)
    - Financial Records- Income & Expense Reports, 1950-1954 (Box 98, Folder 53)
    - Income from Alumnae, 1955 (Box 98, Folder 54)
    - Financial Records- monthly statements, 1936-1942 (Box 98, Folder 55)
    - Financial Records- monthly expense accounts, 1939-1942 (Box 98, Folder 56)
    - Financial Records- store reports, 1938, undated (Box 98, Folder 57)
    - Financial Records- order room/ women's room reports, 1937-1939, undated (Box 98, Folder 58)
    - Financial Records- Treasurer's Reports, 1936-1941 (Box 98, Folder 59)
    - Financial Records- notes on expenses, 1938, undated (Box 98, Folder 60)
    - Financial Records- subscriptions & donations, 1937-1940 (Box 98, Folder 61)
    - Lists of stocks & bonds held, 1928-1945 (Box 98, Folder 62)
    - Property Records- court orders re properties in Brooklyn & Bronx, 1938 (Box 98, Folder 63)
    - Property Records- lists, surveys & analyses of mortgages and certificates held, 1921-1941, undated (Box 98, Folder 64)
    - Property Records- title insurance policies, 1900, 1943 (Box 98, Folder 65)
    - Property Records- 107th Street and 2nd Avenue, mortgage extensions and deed, 1908-1942 (Box 98, Folder 66)
    - Property Records- Budgets for Repairs on 120 W 16th Street and correspondence, 1950-1951 (Box 98, Folder 67)
    - Property Records- 120 W 16th Street, Lease to French YWCA and correspondence, 1926-1941, 1951 (Box 98, Folder 68)
    - Property Records- 120 W 16th Street, correspondence, 1910-1942 (Box 98, Folder 69)
    - Property Records- Appeal to Supreme Court to sell 160 W 16th St, 1954 (Box 98, Folder 70)
    - Property Records- 951 E 214 Street, Bronx, 1939-1941 (Box 98, Folder 71)
    - Property Records- 1861 Cedar Avenue correspondence, 1919-1924 (Box 98, Folder 72)
    - Progress Report, 1954-1955 (Box 98, Folder 73)
    - Proposals for Projects, 1951-1952, undated (Box 98, Folder 74)
    - Publicity, 1951-1955 (Box 98, Folder 75)
  - Subseries 6: Miscellaneous
    - Annual reports- departmental / program, 1955 (Box 99, Folder 1)
    - List of life members, 1951-1952 (Box 99, Folder 2)
    - MKS Retirement- Pension Fund, 1948 (Box 99, Folder 3)
    - Directory of social agencies & civic organizations, Lower West Side Council for Social Planning, 1947 (Box 99, Folder 4)
    - Community Planning Board- minutes, 1954-1955 (Box 99, Folder 5)
    - Greenwich House Counseling Center- reports, 1965-1966 (Box 99, Folder 6)
    - Calendars of Events- Christmas, 1962-1974 (Box 99, Folder 7)
    - Survey to Recruit New Members- questionnaires, 1950 (Box 99, Folder 8)
    - Survey to Recruit New Members- results, 1950 (Box 99, Folder 9)
    - Welfare Council of New York City- memoranda, reports, statements, and programs, 1947 (Box 99, Folder 10)
    - Welfare Council of New York City- memoranda, reports, statements, and programs, undated (Box 99, Folder 11)
    - Neighborhood Campaign, 1947 (Box 99, Folder 12)
    - Inventory, 1947-1948 (Box 99, Folder 13)
    - Inventories, 1949-1952 (Box 99, Folder 14)
    - Inventory, 1954 (Box 99, Folder 15)
    - Inventory, 1955 (Box 99, Folder 16)
    - Inventories, 1964-1966 (Box 99, Folder 17)
    - Inventories, 1970-1976 (Box 99, Folder 18)
    - 16-18 Jones Street- rental to New York Public Library, 1943-1948 (Box 99, Folder 19)
    - Organization Chart, undated (Box 99, Folder 20)
  - Subseries 7: Music School
    - Calendars of Events, 1947-1991 (Box 100, Folder 1)
    - Concert at Town Hall, 1949 (Box 100, Folder 2)
    - Art Show, 1956 (Box 100, Folder 3)
    - Powers' Address to International Music Education Conference, 1970 (Box 100, Folder 4)
    - Amita Scholarship Award Ceremony, 1973 (Box 100, Folder 5)
    - Benefit recital, 1975 (Box 100, Folder 6)
    - Piano Master Class, Karl Schnabel, 1979 (Box 100, Folder 7)
    - 75th Anniversary Celebration, 1981 (Box 100, Folder 8)
    - Commencements, undated, 1949-1951 (Box 100, Folder 9)
    - Student records- exam results, 1947 (Box 100, Folder 10)
    - Student records- exam results, 1948 (Box 100, Folder 11)
    - Student records- exam results, 1949 (Box 100, Folder 12)
    - Student records- exam results, 1949 (Box 100, Folder 13)
    - Student records- report cards, A-Z, 1940s (Box 100, Folder 14)
    - Monday Book 1, undated (Box 100, Folder 15)
    - Monday Book 1, 1950-1951 (Box 100, Folder 16)
    - Tuesday Book 1, undated (Box 100, Folder 17)
    - Tuesday Book 1, 1950-1951 (Box 100, Folder 18)
    - Wednesday Book 2, 1948-1949 (Box 100, Folder 19)
    - Wednesday Book 1, 1950-1951 (Box 100, Folder 20)
    - Wednesday Book, 1950-1951 (Box 100, Folder 21)
    - Thursday Book 1, 1950-1951 (Box 100, Folder 22)
    - Friday Book 1, 1950-1951 (Box 100, Folder 23)
    - Saturday Book 1, 1950-1951 (Box 100, Folder 24)
    - Annual Spring Journal, 1959-1960 (Box 100, Folder 25)
    - Press Releases, 1946-1960 (Box 100, Folder 26)
    - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 100, Folder 27)
    - Catalogues, 1960-1970 (Box 101, Folder 1)
    - Catalogues, 1970-1980 (Box 101, Folder 2)
    - Catalogues, 1980-1990 (Box 101, Folder 3)
    - Catalogues, 1990-1994 (Box 101, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1944-1948 (Box 101, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1948-1951 (Box 101, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1953-1954 (Box 101, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1954-1955 (Box 101, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1957-1958 (Box 101, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1958-1960 (Box 101, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1965-1966 (Box 101, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, 1967-1969 (Box 101, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, 1971-1977 (Box 101, Folder 13)
    - Music School Committee- member lists, undated (Box 101, Folder 14)
    - Minutes, 1947-1958 (Box 101, Folder 15)
    - Director's Reports, 1947-1962 (Box 101, Folder 16)
    - Director's Reports, 1971-1980 (Box 101, Folder 17)
    - Programs, 1947-1949 (Box 101, Folder 18)
    - Programs, 1950-1954 (Box 101, Folder 19)
    - Programs, 1955-1959 (Box 101, Folder 20)
    - Programs, 1960-1964 (Box 101, Folder 21)
    - Programs, 1965-1994 (Box 101, Folder 22)
    - Sarah Arabella Tracy Memorial Fund, 1946-1953 (Box 101, Folder 23)
    - Contributors' lists, 1948-1951, undated (Box 101, Folder 24)
    - List of contributing foundations, 1977 (Box 101, Folder 25)
    - Benefits- list of events and profits, 1967-1975 (Box 101, Folder 26)
    - Budgets, 1946-1948 (Box 101, Folder 27)
    - Personnel Records, A-Z, undated (Box 101, Folder 28)
    - Press releases, 1953-1963 (Box 101, Folder 29)
    - Press releases, 1970-1977 (Box 101, Folder 30)
    - Press releases, 1956-1963, undated (Box 101, Folder 31)
    - Printed materials, undated (Box 101, Folder 32)
    - Radio interview, 1968 (Box 101, Folder 33)
    - Appraisal of furniture, 1961 (Box 101, Folder 34)
    - Dance Workshops- statistical / financial reports, 1965-1966 (Box 101, Folder 35)
    - Music & Dance Workshops, 1974 (Box 101, Folder 36)
    - Newsletter Crescendo, 1947-1948 (Box 101, Folder 37)
    - Newsletter Quarter Notes, 1988 (Box 101, Folder 38)
    - Opera Department, 1950-1955, undated (Box 101, Folder 39)
    - Report on Renovations to Building, ca.1982 (Box 101, Folder 40)
    - Ballet Benefit, 1958 (Box 101, Folder 41)
    - 7th Annual American Music Festival, 1946 (Box 101, Folder 42)
    - Directories with GHMS Listings, 1960, undated (Box 101, Folder 43)
    - Inventories, 1947-1949 (Box 101, Folder 44)
    - Catalogues, 1946-1950 (Box 101, Folder 45)
    - Catalogues, 1950-1960 (Box 101, Folder 46)
    - Art Show- invitations, list of works shown, 1953 (Box 101, Folder 47)
    - Art Show- correspondence, 1953 (Box 101, Folder 48)
    - Art Show- correspondence, 1954 (Box 101, Folder 49)
    - Art Show- lists of ticket buyers/ contributors, 1954 (Box 101, Folder 50)
    - Art Show- lists of works shown; press release; invitation, 1954 (Box 101, Folder 51)
    - Carnegie Hall Concert, 1956 (Box 101, Folder 52)
    - Art Show, 1957 (Box 101, Folder 53)
    - Art Show- correspondence, invitation, 1958-1959 (Box 101, Folder 54)
    - Art Show- financial reports, lists of sponsors, etc., 1958-1959 (Box 101, Folder 55)
    - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 101, Folder 56)
    - Administrative Files and Program Ephemera, 1949-1999; 2015.061 (Box 119)
    - German Diez GHMS Records, Teaching Materials, and Personal Papers, 1950-2014; 2015.061 (Box 123, Box 120, Box 121, Box 122)
    - GHMS Events and Programs Recordings, 1973-1994; 2015.061 (Box 122)
    - German Diez Conducting Batons, undated; 2015.061 (Box 123)
    - Music School Christmas Party Photo Album, undated; 2015.061 (Box 123)
    - Scrapbook in Memory of Edith Newberry, undated; 2015.061 (Box 123)
    - Blueprints: Additions and Alterations to Greenwich House Music School, 1929 (reproductions) (Flat-file-folder 2)
    - Poster: Piano Recital Honoring Claudio Arrau, 2003 (Box Shared Tamiment MSXOS003, Folder 1)
  - Subseries 8: Pottery School
    - Course Catalogues, undated (Box 102, Folder 1)
    - Course Catalogues- summer school, undated (Box 102, Folder 2)
    - Calendars of Events, 1963-1976 (Box 102, Folder 3)
    - Constitution, 1964 (Box 102, Folder 4)
    - Opening Day Ceremony, 1948 (Box 102, Folder 5)
    - Street Party, 1950 (Box 102, Folder 6)
    - Exhibition Catalogues/ programs, 1950s (Box 102, Folder 7)
    - Exhibition Catalogues/ programs, 1970s (Box 102, Folder 8)
    - Exhibits & Sales- printed announcements, 1952-1982 (Box 102, Folder 9)
    - Exhibits & Sales- printed announcements, undated (Box 102, Folder 10)
    - Exhibits & Sales- printed announcements, undated (Box 102, Folder 11)
    - Exhibit- Greenwich House Pottery at Dan Cooper, Inc., 1953 (Box 102, Folder 12)
    - Exhibit- Ceramics by Negoro, 1957 (Box 102, Folder 13)
    - Exhibit- Decorate with Pottery, 1959 (Box 102, Folder 14)
    - Exhibit- Daniel Rhodes show- correspondence, 1960-1962 (Box 102, Folder 15)
    - Exhibit- Daniel Rhodes show, 1962 (Box 102, Folder 16)
    - Exhibit- Argilartists of NY, 1961 (Box 102, Folder 17)
    - Exhibit- Christmas show & sale- applications A-Z, 1964 (Box 102, Folder 18)
    - Exhibit- Annual Juried Exhibition- applications, 1965 (Box 102, Folder 19)